<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dante&#39;s Site</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dante&#39;s Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Whole New World</title>
      <link>/post/2021/05/10/a-whole-new-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/05/10/a-whole-new-world/</guid>
      <description>Someone call the vet, cause these pythons are SICK I used to think that coding languages like Python were completely separate from the statistical stuff I did on R and RStudio. Then I took Computational Biology (SDS348) here at the University of Texas at Austin and I learned so much about R, RMarkdown, and even dabbled into Python (shout out to Dr. Woodward). Here I am going to show y’all how to use reticulate between R and Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aspects of Major</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction For this project, I chose two datasets, the first being “college_recent_grads” which has data about recent college grads who just earned their Bachelors degrees such as, major, major category, median income, unemployment rate, the amount of men and women polled from each major, the total amount of people polled from each major, whether they are employed full or part-time, and what type of job they have. The second is “college_grad_students” which has data about recent graduate school graduates such as, major, major category, median income, unemployment rate, number of people polled for each major, whether they were employed, and if they were employed full-time or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Modeling Instructions A knitted R Markdown document (preferably HTML) and the raw R Markdown file (as .Rmd) should both be submitted to Canvas by :59pm on the due date. These two documents will be graded jointly, so they must be consistent (i.e., don’t change the R Markdown file without also updating the knitted document). In the .Rmd file for Project 2, you can copy the first code-chunk into your project .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
